Guide to the John Watts Papers, 1945-1982 MSS.093
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Peltzer, Dwight, undated (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Phillips, Burrill, undated (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Phillips, Karen, undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Prestamo, Manuel, undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Ragan, Lawrence, undated (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Reilly, Jack, undated (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Rhodes, Lillyan and Daniel, undated (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Roeg, Nicholas, undated (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Rorem, Ned, undated (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Rose, Griffith and Marie-France (1973-76), 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Rose, Griffith and Marie-France (1977-78), 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Rose, Griffith and Marie-France (1979-82), 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Ross, Walter, undated (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Rowe, Catherine, undated (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Russell, undated (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Sanders, Dean, undated (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Schwartz, Elliott, undated (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Schwarz, Gerard, undated (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Singer, Bernard and Sharon, undated (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Tegnell, John Carl, undated (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Thorne, Francis, undated (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Toffler, Alvin, undated (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Tollefson, Arthur, undated (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Trythall, Gil, undated (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Turetzky, Bertram, undated (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Turok, Paul, undated (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Various - Composers Amirkhanian, Charles Austin, Larry Aitken, Robert Amram, David Andrix, George Baksa, Robert Balada, Leonardo Beer, John Bennett, Wilhelmine Ben-Haim, Paul Blank, Allan Bernstein, Leonard Bolz, Harriette Boulez, Pierre Bradshaw, Merrill Brown, Newel Kay Budd, Harold, undated (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Various - Composers: Calabro, Louis Chadabe, Joel Constantinides, Dinos Conrad (unknown surname) Custer, Arthur Denis, Sol Doktor, Paul Elly (unknown surname) Felder, David Fennelly, Brian Fletcher, Grant Fried, George Gumbel, Allen Gideon, Miriam Ginastera, Alberto Glickman, Gene Grant, W. Parks, undated (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Various - Composers: Harris, Roger W. Hartell, John Hartley, Walter Higgins, Dick Huggler, John Ivey, Jean Eichelberger Johnson, Tom Jolas, Betsy Kelly, Robert Kievman, Carson Koch, Fred Koutsoumpas, John Kraft, Leo Krueger, John Kurtz, E. Lane, Richard Levy, Jonathan Luening, Otto Mayer, William Mageau, Sister Mary Magdalen Mason, Lucas McDowell, John Herbert Mennin, Peter Moews, Robert Mongeluzzo, Guy T. Mollicone, Henry Monk, Meredith Morgan, Glen E., undated (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Various - Composers: Persichetti, Vincent Pauls, Gene Penn, William Pone, Gundaris Powell, Morgan Read, Gardner Rolnick, Neil B. Roosevelt, Willard Rubin, Amy D. Schuller, Gunther Schuman, William Schwartz, Charles Sklar, Daniel J. Setapen, Jim Swift, Richard G. Thomson, Virgil Triesch, Judy Wightman, Parks Winsor, Phil Wilding-White, Ray Wuorinen, Charles Yavelow, Christopher, undated (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Composers-Various, undated (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Friends in France, undated (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Friends-Acquaintances., undated-19 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Friends-Acquaintances, undated-19 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - To Watts, as newspaper editor, undated (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - From other newspaper & magazine editors, undated (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Performers-Various, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Performers-Various, undated (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Performers-Various, undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Performers-Various, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Unknown surnames, undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Vermont friends, undated (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Vlahopoulos, Sotireos, undated (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Watts, Elizabeth (daughter), undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Watts, John (From John to various), undated (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Watts, John - Alias Jack Mallory, undated (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Watts, John - Alias S. Stenovsky, undated (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Watts, John (or Laura?) Alias "Lady Boxholder", undated (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Watts and Foreman (to Parents), undated (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - From Watts, John (to Helen Magnuson Watts - 1st wife), undated (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Watts, Helen (1950) (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Watts, Helen (1951) (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Watts, Helen (1951) (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Watts, Mary (1960) 2nd wife, mother of Elizabeth (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Webb, Charles F., undated (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Yannay, Yehuda, undated (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Zupko, Ramon, undated (Box 14, Folder 142)
- Series III: Manuscripts and writings
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 15 - Barcode: 31142042236375 Box 16 - Barcode: 31142042236383
  - Albert, M. (Drawings of Carnegie Hall Concert performance), undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - CCT Review articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Doolittle, Joyce - plays: Aesop's Fable Fair; Golden Goose; Sorcerer's Apprentice, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Doolittle, Joyce - plays: Play Summaries; Beyond the Doubt of a Shadow; Wicked John and the Devil, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Elmslie, Kenward, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Foreman, Laura, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Guptill, Leighton, and Jane Browne, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Hasty, Palmer, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Jahn, Mike, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Manhattan East News - various, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Proposal (by Watts?) for a Light Sculpture, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Rose, Marie-France (poems), undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sargent, E.N., undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Simek, Vasek - Phantasmagoria Historia of D. Johann Fausten (1969) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Singer, Bernard, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Various authors; poems, stories, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Various and unknown authors: poems, stories, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Unknown (Watts?) play - Magnum Opus Nugae, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Unknown - play King Lear, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Zalkind, Ron - prospectus, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Watts - 1833 Seconds, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Watts - ARP class exam, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Wats - Brickman Parody, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Watts - clothing designs, art projects, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Watts - College papers (Cornell dissertation proposal?), undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Watts - Music papers, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Watts - College music papers, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Watts - College music papers, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Watts - College - North Dakota (as a teacher), undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Watts - University of Colorado class notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Watts - University of Tennessee papers, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Watts - College writings, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Watts - Computer Class, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Watts - Dance Book Sketches, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Watts - Drawings 1953 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Watts - Editorials, various, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Watts - Film project notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Watts - Ideas for Avant Garde magazine, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Watts - Ideas for texts (Signals), undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Watts - Marriage vows for wedding to Laura Foreman, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Watts - Mahler research, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Watts - on music, undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Watts - Parody of Mots d'Heures, undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Watts - Performance planning notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Watts - Personal memos - 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Watts - Personal memos - 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Watts - Proposals, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Watts - Proposals, Projects descriptions, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Watts - writing samples (to get journalism jobs), undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Series IV: Biography - John Watts
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 17 - Barcode: 31142042236391
  - Address Books, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Day Planners 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Day Planners 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Day Planner 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Day Planner 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Day Planner 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Day Planner 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Day Planner 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Day Planner 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Day Planner 1982 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hobbies - Glider Pilot, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Medical and Dental Records, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Resumes and Biographies - Watts and Foreman, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Resumes and Works Lists - Watts, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - School - High School Maryville, Tennessee (graduation 1945) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - School - University of Tennessee, Knoxville and Maryville College (1945-49), 1945-1949 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Army Service (1950-52), 1950-1952 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - School - University of Colorado (1950-53), 1950-1953 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - School - Fargo, North Dakota and Ohio (as a teacher) (1957-59), 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - School - Cornell University (1954-59), 1954-1959 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Eron Prep School, New York City (as a teacher) class papers, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Eron Prep School, New York City 1963-65, 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Staten Island College (as a teacher) (1970) (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Watts's Death - (July 1982) Autopsy report (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Watts's Death - Eulogies by friends, told to Laura, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Watts's Death - Funeral, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Watts's Death - Obituaries, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Series V: Business
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 18 - Barcode: 31142042236409 Box 19 - Barcode: 31142042236417 Box 20 - Barcode: 31142042236425 Box 21 - Barcode: 31142042236433 Box 22 - Barcode: 31142042236441 Box 23 - Barcode: 31142042236458 Box 24 - Barcode: 31142042236466 Box 25 - Barcode: 31142042236474
  - Subseries A. General
    - Apartments, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Apartment 25 W. 19th, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Artist Residency - North Carolina, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - American Society of University Composers (A.S.U.C.), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Aware Week 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - BBC-British Broadcasting Corp., undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - BMI- Broadcast Music, Inc., undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Canadian Performing Groups, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Centre de Musique Contemporaine, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Commissions - Sage City Symphony, Vermont, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Competitions: Friedheim Award applications, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Competitions: Pulitzer nomination 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Competitions: Rome Prize application, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Composers Cooperative Society (Watts and friends, pre-cursor to the CCT), undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Composers Cooperative Society 1964-68 receipts, 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Concert Production - (props list for UPS), undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Contracts - Faust Music - Stageplay, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Contracts - Film Music - Daisies; War, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Copyrights, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Fellowship in Prayer (Editorial business), undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - International Imagery Association, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Job Hunting - misc. #1, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Job Hunting - misc. #2, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Job Hunting - Chiquita Gregory/Lahr, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Job Hunting - Japan file, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Job Hunting - Mangold Group, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Legal Documents - Marriage, Divorce, Brith Certificates, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Legal Docs - Estate after death, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Legal Docs - Estate - Libraries, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Legal Docs - The Will and Family problems, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Legal Docs - Wills of JW and LF - not executed, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Legal Docs - Watts vs. Glassover, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Legal Docs - Various, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Manhattan East Newspaper, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Manhattan East, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - May Festivals, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - New School - Course Descriptions, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - New School - Course Descriptions, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - New School - Faculty, Course Descriptions, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - New School - Taubman Class exams, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - New School - Concert Series, memos, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - New School - catalogs, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - New School - catalogs, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Performances of Watts, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Performances of Watts - Electronic Music Festival 1979 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Personal Finances - Income Tax, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Personal Finances - 1974 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Personal Finances - 1981 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Personal Finances - 1981 Europe trip (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Personal Finances - Misc., undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Personal Finances - Misc., undated (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Personal Finances - Misc., undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Personal Finances - Misc., undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Professional Memberships (League of Composers, BMI, Audio Engineering Society), undated (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Publishing - Pop Songs, undated (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Publishing - Joshua, Ellsworth, etc., undated (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Publishing - Misc., undated (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Stationery - artwork for printer, undated (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Trilogy Records, undated (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Trilogy Records, undated (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Trilogy Records - A.F.M. Contracts (Musician's Union), undated (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Trilogy Records - Orders and Mailing List, undated (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Trilogy Records - Ford Foundation Support, undated (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Washington Square Contemp. Music - B. Fennelly, undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - WNYC Radio, undated (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Workshop Residency - Cite, undated (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Workshops - Arts Colonies, undated (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Workshops - Arts Colonies, undated (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Competitions, Grants, Foundations, undated (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - Competitions, Grants, Foundations, undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - CAPS Program (Creative Artists Public Service), undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Ford Foundation, undated (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - Foundation Reject letters 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - Grant Applications - inquiries, undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Guggenheim applications, undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - Guggenheim proposal, undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - League of Composers - ISCM (International Society for Contemporary Music), undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - League of Composers - Financial Report 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - Letters of Recommendation (for Watts), undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - Meet the Composer, undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - NEA (National Endowment for the Arts), undated (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - NEA, undated (Box 21, Folder 82)
    - NEA, undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
    - NEA 1979-80, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 84)
    - NEA 1981-82 (project collaboration w/ Laura Foreman), 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 85)
    - NEH (National Endowment for the Humanities), undated (Box 21, Folder 86)
    - NYSCA (New York State Council for the Arts), undated (Box 21, Folder 87)
    - NYSCA Applications, undated (Box 21, Folder 88)
    - NYSCA 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - NYSCA 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - NYSCA 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - NYSCA 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - NYSCA 1978-79, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 93)
    - Nordic Arts Exchange, undated (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Subseries B: Fundraising
    - Organization Budgets 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Rockefeller Fund, undated (Box 21, Folder 96)
    - Thorne-Hodes Project (Francis Thorne, Stuart Hodes), undated (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Subseries C: Composers and Choreographers Theater (CCT) - General Business
    - Composer and/or score list, undated (Box 22, Folder 98)
    - Creative Projects, undated (Box 22, Folder 99)
    - Donors 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 100)
    - Accounts Receivable 1967-73, 1967-1973 (Box 22, Folder 101)
    - Disbursements 1968-73, 1968-1973 (Box 22, Folder 102)
    - IRS and Taxes, undated (Box 22, Folder 103)
    - Legal, Labor, and Accounting, undated (Box 22, Folder 104)
    - Payroll, undated (Box 22, Folder 105)
    - Tax Guidebooks, undated (Box 22, Folder 106)
    - Guest Book - through 1971 (Box 22, Folder 107)
    - Intern Program, undated (Box 22, Folder 108)
    - Office - Overhead, undated (Box 22, Folder 109)
    - Personnel, Board of Directors, undated (Box 22, Folder 110)
    - Personnel, Board, Weeks, Susan, undated (Box 22, Folder 111)
    - Resumes - Theresa, Latteta, undated (Box 22, Folder 112)
    - Resumes - Misc., undated (Box 22, Folder 113)
    - Tully Hall Concert 1975 (Box 22, Folder 114)
    - Xerox machine, undated (Box 22, Folder 115)
    - CCT Miscellaneous Business, undated (Box 22, Folder 116)
    - CCT Miscellaneous Business, undated (Box 22, Folder 117)
    - CCT Miscellaneous Business, undated (Box 22, Folder 118)
    - CCT Miscellaneous Business, undated (Box 22, Folder 119)
  - Subseries D: CCT Expenditures and Receipts
    - Fiscal Year 1969-70 Receipts, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 120)
    - Fiscal Year 1969-70 Receipts, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 121)
    - Fiscal Year 1970-71 Receipts, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 122)
    - Fiscal Year 1970-71 Receipts, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 123)
    - Fiscal Year 1970-71 Receipts, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 124)
    - Fiscal Year 1970-71 Receipts, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 125)
    - Fiscal Year 1970-71 Cancelled Checks, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 126)
    - Fiscal Year 1971-72 Receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 127)
    - Fiscal Year 1971-72 Receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 128)
    - Fiscal Year 1971-72 Receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 129)
    - Fiscal Year 1971-72 Receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 130)
    - Fiscal Year 1971-72 Cancelled Checks, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 131)
    - Fiscal Year 1972-73 Cancelled Checks - Jan - June 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 132)
    - Fiscal Year 1972-73 Cancelled Checks - July - Sept. 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 133)
    - Fiscal Year 1972-73 Receipts, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 134)
    - Fiscal Year 1972-73 Receipts, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 135)
    - Fiscal Year 1972-73 Receipts, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 136)
    - Fiscal Year 1972-73 Receipts, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 137)
    - Fiscal Year 1973-74 Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 138)
    - Fiscal Year 1973-74 Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 139)
    - Fiscal Year 1973-74 Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 140)
    - Fiscal Year 1973-74 Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 141)
    - Fiscal Year 1973-74 Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 142)
    - Fiscal Year 1973-74 Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 143)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Petty Cash Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 144)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 145)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 146)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 147)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 148)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 149)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 150)
    - Fiscal Year 1974-75 Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 151)
    - Fiscal Year 1975-76 Receipts, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 152)
    - Fiscal Year 1975-76 Receipts, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 153)
    - Fiscal Year 1975-76 Receipts, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 154)
- Series VI: Publicity
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 26 - Barcode: 31142042236482 Box 27 - Barcode: 31142042236490
  - Ads, Flyers, Posters, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Ads, Flyers, Posters, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Ads, Radio & Concert introduction, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Ads, New School, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Ads, New School, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Choreographers Theatre - Foreman press releases, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Concert Production and Promotion, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Concert Promotion - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Foreman Dance - Concert with John Cage 1967 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Foreman Dance - Collaborations with John Watts, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Foreman Dance Company, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Interview with Watts, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Japan House Concert, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - May Festival Composers and Performers, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - May Festival Composers and Performers, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper articles - Colorado, Ohio performances 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper articles - reviews, notices - 1960s - 70s, 1960-1979 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Peltzer, Dwight - publicity info, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Programs 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Programs, Ads, 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Programs, Camp Quago 1965 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Programs, Composers Theatre, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Programs "designed by John", undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Programs, press Dr. Faustus, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Programs, press Aesop's Fable Fair, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Programs, Georgia State Brass Symposium, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Programs, Laugharne; Tully Hall 1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Programs, Tidewater Festival, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Programs, press Time Coded Woman, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Programs for concerts, undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Programs for concerts, undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Programs for concerts, undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Programs for concerts, undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Programs for concerts, undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Programs for concerts, undated (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Program Notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Program Notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Reviews, undated (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Reviews, undated (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Reviews - Trilogy Records, undated (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Sanders, Dean - publicity info, undated (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Wallwork - publicity, undated (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Wallwork - Program notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Watts specific publicity #1, undated (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Watts specific publicity #2, undated (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Watts specific publicity #3, undated (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Series VII: Printed Material
  Scope and Contents note
  [for oversize items in Series VII, see Boxes 86, 87]